Guide to the Edward A. Feigenbaum Papers SC0340
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2005-101
  - Stanford materials
    - Building Blocks Artificial Intelligence book project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Permissions, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Permissions: Re: Building Blocks Article, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Amarel, Saul--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Bledsoe, Woodrow--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Bobrow, Daniel--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Brachman, Ronald--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Brown, John Seeley--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Buchanan, Bruce--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Bundy, Alan--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Davis, Randall--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Duda, Richard--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Fikes, Richard--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Fuchi, Kazuhiro--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - Gerlenter, Herb--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Green, Cordell--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Hewitt, Carl--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - Kanade, Takeo--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - Kowalski, Robert--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - Lederberg, Joshua--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - Lenat, Douglas--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 31)
      - Levesque, Hector--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - McCarthy, John--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 33)
      - Michie, Donald--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 34)
      - Minsky, Marvin--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - Mitchell, Thomas--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - Moses, Joel--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - Newell, Alan--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 38)
      - Nilsson, Nils--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 39)
      - Raphael, Bert--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 40)
      - Quillian, M. Ross--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 41)
      - Reddy, Raj--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 42)
      - Roberts, Lawrence--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 43)
      - Rosen, Charles--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 44)
      - Rosenschein, Stanley--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 45)
      - Sacerdoti, Earl--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 46)
      - Samuel, Arthur--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 47)
      - Schank, Roger--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 48)
      - Shaw, J. Clifford--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 49)
      - Shortliffe, Edward--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 50)
      - Simon, Herbert--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 51)
      - Stefik, Mark--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 52)
      - Sussman, Gerry--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 53)
      - Waterman, Donald--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 54)
      - Winograd, Terry--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 55)
      - Winston, Patrick--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 56)
      - Woods, William--Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 57)
      - Building Blocks of Artificial Intelligence (AI) Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 58)
      - Building Blocks Book, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 59)
      - Pederson: Building Blocks Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 60)
      - Building Blocks "A" Book Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 61)
      - Materials for Talks and Papers, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 62)
      - Building Blocks source papers (1 of 6) (Box 38, Folder 63)
      - Building Blocks source papers (2 of 6) (Box 38, Folder 64)
      - Building Blocks source papers (3 of 6) (Box 38, Folder 65)
      - Building Blocks source papers (4 of 6) (Box 38, Folder 66)
      - Building Blocks source papers (5 of 6) (Box 38, Folder 67)
      - Building Blocks source papers (6 of 6) (Box 38, Folder 68)
    - Large Multiuse Knowledge Base (LMKB)--Misc communications and papers, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Large Multiuse Knowledge Bases (LMKB) Goals formulation, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - DENDRAL-64 Part 1: Topological Mapping of Organic Molecules, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - DENDRAL-64 Part 2, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Misc. Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Papers, 1979-1989 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Misc. Course materials, 1982-1984 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Transparencies--EPAM Historical Materials, undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Papers with H. Simon--EPAM Historical Materials, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - EPAM File- EPAM Historical Materials, 1967-1969 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - EPAM Talks, Notes- EPAM Historical Materials, 1960s (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - EPAM III--EPAM Historical Materials, 1960s (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - "An Information-Processing Theory of Some Effects of Similiarity, Familiarization, and Meaningfulness in Verbal Learning"--EPAM Historical Materials, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - EPAM Papers--EPAM Historical Materials, 1960s (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) / HPP, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Blackboard Notes--CS 123 Possible Talk, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - EAF and Penny Nii--Bios, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) in Kyoto, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Advanced Architectures Proposal to NASA-Ames, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Advanced Architectures Reports, Papers, Summaries #1, 1981-1985 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Advanced Architectures Reports, Papers, Summaries #2, 1981-1985 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Advanced Architectures Working Project Notes, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Advanced Architectures--CAGE and TINA Reports / Summaries, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Advanced Architectures--Quarterly Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Advanced Architectures Readings #1, 1981-1985 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Advanced Architectures Readings #2, 1981-1985 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Advanced Architectures Readings #3, 1981-1985 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Advanced Architectures Readings #4, 1981-1985 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Advanced Architectures Readings #5, 1981-1985 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Artificial Intelligence (AI) Architectures--Reading, 1981-1985 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - EAF Talk--Why Not the Best / Blackboard, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - CS Class Materials, 1976-1978 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - EAF Talks--Artificial Intelligence (AI) Lectures, 1980s (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - CS 224, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Herbert Simon Papers #1, 1969-1980 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Herbert Simon Papers #2, 1969-1980 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Herbert Simon Papers #3, 1969-1980 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Centennial--Stanford, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University Alumni, Venezuela, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Informatica 85, Sao Paulo, Brazil, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Senator John Glenn, Stanford--Computer Science Department (CSD), 1985 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - SU Exec. Stanford, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - SU Graduation, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Computer Forum, Stanford, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Political Military, Stanford--Hoover, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - HPP Visitors, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - HPP Visitor, Thanks, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 48)
    - HPP Visitor, Dr. Jerome Rubin ARDC, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 49)
    - HPP Visitors, Artificial Intelligence (AI) Steering Committee, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 50)
    - HPP Visitor, SUWA, Motoi, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 51)
    - HPP Visitor, WATANABE, Masanobu, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 52)
    - Pasternak, Stanford, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 53)
    - HPP Visitor, Navelex, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 54)
    - HPP Visitors, Hitachi, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 57)
    - HPP Visitor, Doug Smith--ONR, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 58)
    - BBC, SU--Visitors, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 59)
    - HPP Visitors, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 60)
    - Visitor, Matsuyama, Takashi, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 61)
    - SU President's Lunch, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 70)
    - Stanford Japan Center Conference, Kyoto, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 78)
    - CMU, CSD Advisory Board--Pittsburgh, PA, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 79)
    - Stanford Law / Computer Seminar, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 85)
    - President Mitterand, Stanford, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Stanford Alumni, NYC, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Breakfast, Stanford--Buck House, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Publisher's Course, Stanford, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - "Managing the Computer Potential", Stanford, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Business Alumni, Stanford, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Stanford Forum, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 51)
    - Stanford Eng. Exec. Program, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 72)
    - CSD Retreat, Pajaro Dunes, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - CSD Retreat, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - "An Information Processing Theory of Verbal Learning"--EAF's Carnegie Mellon Thesis, published by RAND Corporation, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - "The Heuristic Dendral Program for Explaining Emperical Data" by Bruce G. Buchanan, Joshua Lederberg, Co-Principal Investigators: E. Feigenbaum, J. Lederberg, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - "On Generality and Problem Solving: A Case Study Using the Dendral Program" by Edward A. Feigenbaum, Bruce G. Buchanan, Joshua Lederberg, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Advanced Architectures--Expert Systems on Multiprocessor Architectures--Papers and Communications, 1986--1989 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Advanced Architectures--Quarterly Reports to USAF, 19886--1987 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Advanced Architectures--Proceedings: Expert Systems Workshop, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Advanced Architectures--Intel: Programming Concurrent Computers Workshop, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, Aug.--Dec. 1989 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, Jan.--July 1989 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, Jan.-Dec. 1988 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, Sept. 1984-July 1985 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, April-Sept. 1984 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, Oct. 1983-April 1984 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, May-Sept. 1983 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, Aug. 1982-May 1983 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, Mar. 1981-June 1982 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, May 1980-Mar. 1981 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, Sept.--May 1980 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, May 1979-Oct. 1980 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, July 1977-May 1979 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, Jan.-July 1977 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, Dec. 1985-Oct. 1986 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, Aug.-Dec. 1987, Aug.-Dec. 1985 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - EAF Printed Correspondence, Jan.-Aug. 1987 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - EAF Original Email Correspondence, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - HPP Retreat folder--Project Reviews, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Trip Itineraries, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Sunrise Club Talk (EAF Talk), 1987 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - CS 225--Artificial Intelligence (AI) Notes, 1965--1976 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Feigenbaum Historical--DENDRAL-- Artificial Intelligence (AI) Journal, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Advanced Architectures Book Project 1/2, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Advanced Architectures Book Project 2/2, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Stanford letterhead, undated (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Thesis--Automated Modeling of Physical Systems--P. P. Nayak, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Thesis--Use of Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Simple Mathmatics to Analyze a Physiological Model--J. C. Kunz, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Thesis--Planning with Constraints--M. J. Stefik, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Thesis--VM: Representing Time-Dependent Relations in a Medical Setting--L. M. Fagan, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Thesis--Monitoring System Behavior in a Complex Computational Environment--M. L. Model, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Thesis--Prototypes and Production Rules: A Knowledge Representation for Computer Consultations--J. S. Aikins, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Thesis--Automatic Construction of Algorithims and Data Structures Using a Knowledge Base of Programming Rules--D. R. Barstow, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Thesis--Version Spaces: An Approach to Concept Learning--T. M. Mitchell, 1978 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Thesis--Heuristic Reasoning About Uncertainty: An Artificial Intelligence Approach--P. R. Cohen, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Thesis--Reasoning by Analogy with Applications to heuristic Problem Solving: A Case Study--R. E. King, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Thesis--A Decision-Theoretic Approach to Heuristic Planning--C. P. Langlotz, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Thesis--Knowledge-based Expirament Design in Molecular Genetics - P. E. Friedland, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Thesis--Discovery and Representation of Causal Relationships from a Large Time-Oriented Clinical Database: The RX Project--R. L. Blum, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Thesis--Mycin: A Rule-Based Computer Program for Advising Physicians Regarding Antimicrobial Therapy Selection--E. H. Shortliffe, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Thesis--Query optimization by Semantic Reasoning--J. J. King, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Thesis--Use of Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Simple Mathematics to Analyze a Psysiological Model--J. C. Kunz, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Thesis--Irrelevance Reasoning in Knowledge Based Systems--A. Y. Levy, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Thesis--Contexts: A Formalization and Some Applications--R. V. Guha, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL)--Kyoto Proposal, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Kyoto, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - "Knowledge Engineering: Applied Side of Artificial Intelligence (AI)" by EAF, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - "An Introduction to Knowledge Engineering, Blackboard Model, and AGE" by Penny Nii, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Email transcripts--EAF, Nii, Barr, Friedland, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - EAF Correspondence, 1982--1984 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - CSD Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - 25th Anniversary of the DENDRAL Project--Feigenbaum, Smith, Carhart, Sutherland--Session #1 1/2--Stanford Instructional Television Network (SITN), circa 1990; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - 25th Anniversary of the DENDRAL Project--Feigenbaum, Smith, Carhart, Sutherland--Session #1 2/2--Stanford Instructional Television Network (SITN), circa 1990; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - 25th Anniversary of the DENDRAL Project--Lederberg, Stefik, Masinter, Sridharan, Altman, Johnson--Session #2 1/2--Stanford Instructional Television Network (SITN), circa 1990; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - 25th Anniversary of the DENDRAL Project--Lederberg, Stefik, Masinter, Sridharan, Altman, Johnson--Session #2 2/2--Stanford Instructional Television Network (SITN), circa 1990; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - 25th Anniversary of the DENDRAL Project--Buchanan, Barr, Friedland, Clancy, Bennett, Dietterich, Kunz, Englemore--Session #3 1/2--Stanford Instructional Television Network (SITN), circa 1990; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - 25th Anniversary of the DENDRAL Project--Buchanan, Barr, Friedland, Clancy, Bennett, Dietterich, Kunz, Englemore--Session #3 2/2--Stanford Instructional Television Network (SITN), circa 1990; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - 25th Anniversary of the DENDRAL Project--Lenat, Davis, Wiederhold, Hart, Amarel, Flatt, Levinthal, Bobrow, Rindfleisch--Session #4 1/2 - Stanford Instructional Television Network (SITN), circa 1990; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - 25th Anniversary of the DENDRAL Project--Lenat, Davis, Wiederhold, Hart, Amarel, Flatt, Levinthal, Bobrow, Rindfleisch--Session #4 2/2 - Stanford Instructional Television Network (SITN), circa 1990; 1 videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Adv. Arch Meeting--Delagi, 1989; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Adv. Arch Meeting, 1989; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Adv. Arch Meeting, 1989; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Adv. Arch Proj.--Penny 1, 1989; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Adv. Arch Proj.--Penny 2, 1989; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Larry Walker, spoke in EAF's class, 1991; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - CS226 John Shock, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - CS226 Rick Hayes Roth #1, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 32)
    - CS226 Rick Hayes Roth #2, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 33)
    - CS226 Peter Hart (Short), undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 34)
    - CS226 Peter hart, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 35)
    - CS226 Ed Mahler, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 36)
    - CS226 Ed Mahler, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 37)
    - CS226 Ed Mahler, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 38)
    - CS226 Paul Harmon #1, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 39)
    - CS226 Paul Harmon #2, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 40)
    - Wolfgang--3 Compositions, Riechen, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 41)
    - CS226 Monte Zweben #1, 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 42)
    - CS226 Monte Zweben #2, 1994; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 43)
    - CS226 Avron Barr #1, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 44)
    - CS226 Avron Barr #2, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 45)
    - CS226 Karl Wiig #1, undated; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 72, Folder 46)
    - Computer files-Laboratory documents, mostly by Penny Nii, circa 1990; 19 computer media (Box 72, Folder 48)
    - Expert Systems: Buchanan--good section on KA, good early section statring with "Small Systems", undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Graphical Access to Expert Systems: Examples from the Oncocin System, 1986; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - ONCOCIN (Beta Tape), undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - Knowledge Engineering: AI Research at Stanford HPP--Stanford Computer Forum, Distinguished Lectures Series [PAL format], 1985; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Plenary Session 1: Rindfleisch, Shortliffe 1/2, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Plenary Session 1: Rindfleisch, Shortliffe 2/2, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Parallel Session 1A: Rindfleisch, Buchanan, Clearwater 1/2, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Parallel Session 1A: Rindfleisch, Buchanan, Clearwater 2/2, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Parallel Session 1B: Fagan, Cooper 1/2, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Parallel Session 1B: Fagan, Cooper 2/2, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Parallel Session 2: Feigenbaum, Keller, Hayes-Roth 1/2, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Parallel Session 2: Feigenbaum, Keller, Hayes-Roth 2/2, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Parallel Session 2A: Nii, Cornelius 1/3, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Parallel Session 2A: Nii, Cornelius 2/3, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Parallel Session 2A: Nii, Cornelius 3/3, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Parallel Session 2B: Delagi, Brown, Byrd 1/3, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Parallel Session 2B: Delagi, Brown, Byrd 2/3, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Knowledge Systems Laboratory (KSL) Day Parallel Session 2B: Delagi, Brown, Byrd 3/3, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #1, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Use copy, 1988; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 77, Folder 1.1)
      - Duplicating master, 1 computer file(s) (mov)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #2, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Duplicating master, 1 computer file(s) (mov)
      - Use copy, 1988; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 77, Folder 2.1)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #3, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Duplicating master, 1 computer file(s) (mov)
      - Use copy, 1988; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 77, Folder 3.1)
      - CS 408 Feigenbaum #6 Roundtable--Barr, EAF, Englemore, Wogrin, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - Duplicating master, 1 computer file(s) (mov)
        - Use copy, 1988; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 77, Folder 5.1)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #5 Nancy Wolgrin, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #7 Paul Harmon, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #8 Northrop (Lindsay / Joy), 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #9 Intellipath, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Duplicating master, 1 computer file(s) (mov)
      - Use copy, 1988; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 77, Folder 8.1)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #10 FMC--Thorndyke, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #11 Kunz--Intellicorp, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #12 IBM, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #13 Wogrin, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #14 DEC--Jack Rahaim, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #15 Fagan--ONCOCIN, OPAL, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #16 Levitt, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #17 Branscom, Hart, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #18 Dupont--Mahler, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - CS 408 Feigenbaum #19 Navistar, 1988; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - CS 226 Feigenbaum # 1Chukyo University--Stanford Instructional Television Network, 1989; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - CS 226 Feigenbaum # 2 Chukyo University--Stanford Instructional Television Network, 1989; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - CS 226 Feigenbaum # 3 Chukyo University--Stanford Instructional Television Network, 1989; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - CS 226 Feigenbaum # 4 Chukyo University--Stanford Instructional Television Network, 1989; 1 videotape(s) (Box 77, Folder 22)